瑞典情报部门特工无权杀人
The Swedish intelligence service has no agents who are licensed to kill.
任何情况下都不允许
It must not happen under any circumstances.
除非出于自卫或涉及到国家利益
Except in self-defense or if it is in the Nation's interest.
你又做噩梦了
You had a bad dream again.
我吵醒你了？
Did I wake you?
没
No.
为何你不能告诉我你要去哪儿？
Why can't you tell me where you're going?
因为我不想骗你
Because I won't lie to you.
那就别骗...
Don't then ...
告诉我实话
tell me the truth.
我会回来的
I'm coming back.
四个月后
Four months later.
乌兹别克斯坦，阿富汗边境
Uzbekistan, on the border of Afghanistan.
丹尼索夫，丹尼索夫...
Denisov, Denisov...
我能看出你在虚张声势
I know when someone is bluffing.
你一厢情愿罢了
It's just what you think.
我从你眼里看出来的
I see it in your eyes.
正如我妈妈常说的
As my mom used to say,
如果你相信女人
"If you trust women,"
那你将死于贫穷
"you die poor."
如果你相信男人
"If you trust men,"
那你将英年早逝
"you die young."
你母亲是个聪明的女人
Your mother was a wise woman.
你个混蛋...真是狗屎运！
You bastard ... What a hell of luck you have!
“钞票先生”教会了我一切
Mr. Green has taught me everything I know.
钞票先生，美元先生
Mr. Green, Mr. Dollar.
钞票是个好东西
Mr. Green is a good man.
准备好了，我们明天出发
We're set. We go tomorrow.
很好...这鬼地方让我开始感到不舒服了
That's good ... This fucking place is starting to get on my nerves.
干杯！
Cheers!
克洛托夫，把东西拿出来
Krutov, take out the goods.
跟我走
Follow me.
你有多少货？
How many do you have?
照约定，200枚
As agreed. 200 pieces.
如果你有正确坐标
If you have the correct coordinates,
你可以打中80公里外的美国人
you can hit an American in the head 80-kilometers away.
把它们搬走
Take them away.
下来
Come on.
帮忙
Help.
- 丹尼索夫是你的真名？ - 是啊
- Denisov, is that your real name? - Yes.
是吗？你知道这是什么吗？
Yeah? You know what this is?
面朝卡车！
Face against the truck!
土匪！
Bandits!
查卡
Chaka.
有个人不见了，是司机谢尔盖
There is one guy who's missing, the driver Sergei.
那我的钱呢？
So where is my money?
司机不见了，找到他！
The driver's missing. Find him!
去追他！
After him!
片名：《汉密尔顿：国家利益》
军事安全情报部门，斯德哥尔摩
Military Intelligence and Security...Stockholm.
不明身份团伙
So an unknown group,
原来是欧洲头号遭通缉的武器走私集团
turns out to be Europe's most wanted weapons smuggling organization.
而且跟丢了200枚天幕迫击炮弹
And 200 Sky Shadow mortars go missing.
我这样想没错吧？
Is that what I'm supposed to think?
确实如此
That's what happened.
你的任务是...
Your mission was...
看住这些瑞典制
to watch over the Swedish-made
GPS制导炮弹
GPS guided shells,
防止它们落入敌手
so they would not fall into the wrong hands.
但它们还是失踪了而且你不知道在哪
And yet they have disappeared and you don't know where.
情况不是这样的对吗？
That's not really what happened is it?
汉密尔顿的任务是
Hamilton's mission was
摸清武器贩卖网络
to map the networks dealing with weapons.
那是你给他的任务
Tthat was the mission you gave him,
但过去三个月我已成为行动指挥官
but for the last 3 months I have been the operational commander.
却仍未有人来跟我说这网络的事
And still I have not been informed of these networks.
迪米特里和买家遭袭击身亡
Dimitri and the one who was to buy them were killed in the attack.
这也许是你没摸清情况
Then, perhaps your mapping was not so good.
先生们
Gentlemen.
他是新人，新官上任三把火嘛
He's new ... and has to show off.
我们私下说说，你对这团伙有何看法？
Between us ... What is your take on this group?
组织严密，手法专业
Well-organized. Professionals.
我杀的那个人手上戴了个手表
The man I had taken out had a watch on...
是鲁美诺斯军表 （美军海豹部队专用表）
a Luminox.
他们似乎是美国的
They seemed to be U.S.
特种部队，很可能是海豹部队
Special soldiers, most likely Navy Seals.
- 美国人！ - 可能吧
- Americans! - Maybe.
阿乌贝里，埃塞俄比亚
Awubere, Ethiopia.
看见没，就这样操作
See, it comes up like that.
按下F，发送，好吗？
Press F... Send, OK?
我马上去找我兄弟
Right now I'm going to get the coordinates
拿坐标，好吗？你拿着炮弹
from my buddy, ok? You hang on to that.
你弄到坐标了吗？
You got the coordinates?
这些是正确GPS坐标吗？
- Are these the correct GPS coordinates?
嗯
- Uh huh.
- 那里有许多人啊 - 我们可以走了
- It's densely populated. - We're set to go.
那是他的家，本来这是要打赛德尔玛的
That's his home. The hit was supposed to happen with Sidalman.
计划有变
Change in plans.
拜托伙计...萨马塔・拉希姆有两个孩子...
Come on man... Samata Rahim has two children ...
没门，我不杀孩子的
No way ... I do not murder children ...
他们会承担所有责任的，你什么都不用做
- They'll take all the blame. You're not doing anything.
我刚告诉他怎么使用坐标，这又算什么？
- I just instructed him how to use the coordinates.And? ...
里，没时间质疑命令了
Lee, This is no time to question orders.
那个叫阿布杜拉还是什么的，给你坐标
Abdullah whatever your fuckin' name is. Here are the coordinates.
在这等
Wait here.
- 嘿！ - 嘿，本杰明
- Hey! - Hey Benjamin,
- 一切还好吧？ - 是的
- Everything ok? - Yeah.
能回家真好
Oh, it shall be so nice to get home.
我得给孩子们补上礼物
I have to fix some presents to the kids.
记得提醒我在机场买点东西
- Remind me to pick up something at the airport.
没问题
- No problem.
天啊
Jesus ...
下车！
Get out of the car!
- 你不会想这样做的 - 给我滚下车！
- You're not gonna warn him. - Get out of the goddam car!
现在如何？
Now what?
你要藏起来？我们会找到你的！
You going to hide? We'll find you!
你知道自己没法人间蒸发的
You know you can't disappear.
现在把枪给我
Now give me the gun.
- 退后！ - 天啊！
- Back off! - Jesus!
否则下一枪就要打你头了
Or the next shot goes right between the eyes.
- 什么？ - 拉格贝克，到前面来
- What? - Lagerback, get over here.
快，马上！
Come on, now!
- 好吧 - 开车！
- Ok. - Drive!
我说开车！
I said drive!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
但是我本不想拉你下水的
But it was not my intention to drag you into this.
拉我下什么水？
Drag me into what?
我们共事了一个月
We worked together for a month,
突然间你像个疯子似的掏出枪来，什么情况？
all of a sudden you pull a gun like a maniac. What's going on?
拉格贝克
Lagerback ...
你曾是塞彻贡的技术顾问
You've been technical advisor for Sectragon,
它一直在训练恐怖分子
who in turn have been training terrorists.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
塞彻贡会用一切手段来追杀我
Sectragon will come after me with everything they got.
那这就是你需要我的原因，我是，我是你的人质？
So that's what you need me for, I'm, I'm your hostage?
不！
No!
是为了你的安全，我不能跟你细说了
But for your own safety, I can't tell you any more.
现在我要去吉布提
Now I'm going to Djibouti.
从那儿你可以安全回瑞典
From there you can get a safe way back home to Sweden.
我们可以和平解决的
We can work something out.
你可以拿走我的钱，你可以把钱留着！
You can take my money ... You can have the money!
他说什么了？怎么回事？
What did he say? What's happening?
瑞典...我是瑞典公民
Sweden ... I am a Swedish citizen
你走错边境了，这是索马里！
You are on the wrong side of the border, this is Somalia!
索德医院，斯德哥尔摩
Soder Hospital. Stockholm.
我希望你今晚不用过来
I hope you won't have to come in tonight.
拜，回见！
Bye, see you!
是他吗？
Is it him?
- 嗯 - 祝你好运
- Mmm. - Good luck.
你来干嘛？
What do you want?
来看你
To see you.
四个月后才来？
After four months?
得了吧
Forget it.
你说得对
You're right.
我还没告诉你我是谁
I haven't told you who I am.
我做什么的
What I'm doing.
为什么我消失了
Why I disappear.
但是我从没对你撒谎
But I never told you lies.
是没，但是...
No, but ...
这都四个月了
for four months.
我会解释的
I'll try to explain,
如果你愿意听的话
if you're willing to listen.
你曾化作俄国人
You have lived as Russian
跟武器走私犯住一起？
with weapons smugglers?
你是个间谍
You're a spy.
我是个情报人员
I'm an intelligence officer.
是的
Yes
我还以为你是搞婚外恋什么的
I thought you were cheating on your wife or something like that.
自我走后我就每天都在想你
I've thought about you every day since I left.
如果你不想这样过日子
I understand if you can't handle it anymore.
如果你不想见我我也理解
If you don't want to see me.
但是我想见你
But I wanted to see you.
当我出差在外时
When I was over there,
这段时间，它...
this time, it ...
它让我想了很多
it made me think.
想了什么？
About what?
我想改变我的生活
That I want to change my life.
你想变成怎样的？
What would you change it to?
我想跟你一起生活
I want to live my life with you.
那就是我想干的
That's what I want to do.
其他事我都做完了
I've done the other.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
我们在索马里出了点问题
We have a problem in Somalia.
我们在等政府的许可命令
We are waiting for the go-ahead from the government,
等着通知该如何处理
about how it should be handled.
我会安排好给你所有信息的
I will arrange it so that you get all the info.
这可能跟阿富汗有关
It might be a link to Afghanistan.
准备再去一次吧
Get ready to go again.
你跟踪我了？
Are you having me followed?
不
No.
- 不是我认识的人 - 我会查查看的
- It's not someone I recognize. - I'll check it out.
我也会查查玛丽的
And I'll check out Mary as well.
她是离开瑞典前你接触的最后一人
She was the last one you were with before you left Sweden.
你到底是怎么知道这事的？
How the hell do you know about that?
- 你觉得她跟这事有关？ - 你认为呢？
- Do you think that she's involved? - What do you think?
我认为你错了
I think you're wrong.
我会过去的
I'm coming.
注意安全
Be careful.
拜
Bye.
我刚在打电话
I'm on call.
我有个紧急手术，所以我得...
I have an emergency surgery, so I have to go into ...
好的
Ok.
你呆在这儿！
You stay here!
待会我会做早饭
I'm going to make breakfast later.
首相办公室，斯德哥尔摩
Prime Minister's Office. Stockholm.
那我们不知道拉格贝克在哪？
So we don't know where Lagerback is?
或是他是否还活着？
Or whether he's alive?
你有什么新消息吗？
Have you gotten any new information?
是的，拉格贝克在索马里
Yes. Lagerback is in Somalia.
遭关押了
Imprisoned.
- 遭关押了？ - 是
- Imprisoned? Yes.
好吧
Yep.
克拉斯・奥洛夫松
Clas Olofsson.
拉格贝克在埃塞俄比亚干嘛的？
What was Lagerback doing in Ethiopia?
拉格贝克当时在那做私人旅行
Lagerback was there on a personal trip.
他在索马里边境失踪
He disappeared on the border with Somalia.
作为私人旅行目的地来说
Isn't that an extremely dangerous region
那不是非常危险的区域吗？
to choose as a private destination?
当前我们没有关于他囚禁情况的进一步消息
We have no further details about his captivity at the moment.
您认为他的失踪
Do you think that his work with you on
跟你们一起做的高科技武器研究
advanced high-tech weapons may have something
- 可能有关吗？ - 不，我不这样认为
- to do with his disappearance? - No. I don't think so.
但是这确实是个不容忽视的疑点
But that's a suspicion that's just hard to ignore.
您作为北佛斯的副主任，应该知道
You as deputy director at the North Fors, should really know
他在那儿做什么
what he was doing there.
马丁・拉格贝克负责“教学任务”
Martin Lagerback worked with education.
所有北佛斯工业的员工都希望政府
All of us at the North Fors Industries hope that the government
尽全力营救以使其尽快与家人团聚
do their utmost so that he may soon be reunited with his family.
首相阁下，您认为此事会
Do you think, Prime Minister, that this
影响即将召开的和平会议吗？
can get in the way of the coming peace conference?
此外，受此影响，埃塞俄比亚总理约瑟夫・贝克勒
This, among other things, Ethiopia's prime minister, Josef Bekele
- 会出席会议吗？ - 开炮！
- will be there? - Fire!
此次会议是约瑟夫・贝克勒
The conference is an opportunity for Josef Bekele
和其他政党在该地区共创稳定局面的机会
and the other parties to create stability in the region.
作为部长，因为牵涉到北佛斯工业
Will you, as Minister, now take a closer look at your appointments
您打算履行职责
since North Fors Industries is involved,
彻查它们是否与
in order to see if there are links
- 该地区国家有关吗？ - 额，不
- to the countries in the region? - Hmm, uh, no.
因为拉格贝克的失踪与它们的生意无关
Since Lagerback's disappearance has nothing to do with business.
- 所以.... - 我问的不是那个
- So ... - That's not what I asked.
政府不打算调查北佛斯否认
Will the government not investigate North Fors' denial that Lagerback
拉格贝克公费前往埃塞俄比亚谈生意的声明吗？
was there in Ethiopia on business at their expense?
瑞典牵涉到该地区
The idea that Sweden would be involved
武器贸易的说法纯属无稽之谈
in the handling of weapons in the region is ridiculous.
瑞典从未
Sweden has never
也绝不会允许向交战国家出售武器
and will never approve weapons to warring countries.
那你认为我们该雇佣安保公司？
So you think we should employ a security company?
派雇佣兵去救拉格贝克？
A private army to rescue Lagerback?
嗯，但不是我们，而是北佛斯工业
Mmm. Well no, not us, but North Fors Industries.
克拉斯・奥洛夫松联系我提供了这个建议
Clas Olofsson contacted me and suggested this idea.
这具体要怎么操作？
How would it really take place?
萨拉...
Sara ...
让塞彻贡处理吧，他们是专业的
let Sectragon take care of this. They are pros.
两年前
Two years ago,
塞彻贡救出了
Sectragon saved
6个援建哥伦比亚的荷兰工人
six Dutch aid workers in Colombia,
并且去年在摩加迪沙救了两个法国医生
and last year there were two French doctors in Mogadishu.
我需要瑞典人
I want a Swedish person.
一个对这种事有经验的人
Someone with experience in situations like this.
好的
Yes.
凶手带走了一些照片
The killer has taken some photographs.
可能是与她有关的某个波兰人
Probably someone from Poland who contacted her.
我相信凶手在故意误导我们
I believe that the killer is trying to lead us astray.
玛利亚醒过来
Maria had awakened.
她被电话叫到医院
She was called to come in,
在23:45时
at 23:45.
离开前她为何要整理床铺？
Why would she make her bed before she left?
是的，也许她并没睡觉
Yes, perhaps she had not gone.
- 是吧？ - 不，不
What? - No no.
值班医生会在休息时尽量多睡
The doctor on duty sleeps when she can.
她怎么买得起这公寓？
How did she afford this apartment?
值班医生
The doctor on duty,
你知道的...“好工作，好生活”
You know ... "Go to work, get a life."
你的飞机两小时内起飞
Your plane leaves in about two hours.
你先看，然后我们谈谈细节
Read, then we'll go over the details.
警方有什么动静？
What do the police think?
你让凶案看起来跟波兰有关
You made it look like the killer has links to Poland.
公寓很干净，没有凶器
The apartment is clean, the murder weapon is gone
没有犯罪证据
there is no incriminating evidence.
玛丽是无辜的
Mary was innocent.
你不忘记这事就没法开展工作
You can't do this, unless you can get past this.
萨马塔・拉希姆
Samata Rahim.
索马里流亡政治家
Somalian exiled politician.
他昨天在炸弹袭击中身亡
He was killed in a bomb attack yesterday.
无人声明对此负责
No one has accepted the blame.
看看吧
Take a look.
马丁・拉格贝克
Martin Lagerback.
北佛斯工业雇员
Employed by North Fors Industries.
他精通GPS和激光制导武器
He specializes in GPS and laser-guided weapons.
被索马里民兵抓获
He was taken by Somali militia.
北佛斯已经派
North Fors has appointed
塞彻贡去救他了
Sectragon to free him.
我确信
I am convinced
那些在阿富汗失踪的天幕炮弹
that these Sky Shadow weapons that disappeared in Afghanistan
现在就在索马里
are now located in Somalia.
你要在拉格贝克获救后跟着他
You should be with Lagerback when he's released,
确保他回到瑞典
and make sure he comes home to Sweden.
你飞去吉布提
You fly to Djibouti.
我要先去贝鲁特几个小时
I need a few hours in Beirut.
如果我来做，就得按我的办法来
If I do this, then I do it my way.
带拉格贝克回来，别绕道
Get home Lagerback, no detours.
这是曼斯菲尔德的要求
It was Mansfield's security requirements.
别让他来烦我
Keep him away from me.
他对降落在贝鲁特会感到不高兴的
He's not going to be happy with that, landing in Beirut.
贝鲁特，黎巴嫩
Beirut. Lebanon.
- 莫娜，气色不错啊！ - 你看起来很累
- Mona, looking great! - You look tired.
我需要走后门
I need a back door.
我在索马里有联络人，他叫查德
I have a contact in Somalia. His name is Chad.
- 塔里克你还在这混呢 - 汉密尔顿先生
- Tareq you're still hanging around. - Mr. Hamilton.
卡尔...
Carl ...
这跟使用瑞典制武器的埃塞俄比亚恐怖袭击有关吗？
Is this about the terror attack in Ethiopia, using Swedish weapons?
我们可能老了，不过我们还没瞎呢
We might be small, but we are not blind.
有高科技武器的恐怖分子不是个好兆头啊
Terrorists with high-tech weapons is not a good sign.
恐怖分子？
Terrorists?
嗯，所有事都指向索马里的青年党 （伊斯兰激进组织）
Well, everything about this points to Al-Shabab in Somalia.
显然你比我知道得多
Apparently you know more than I do.
事情不妙
That's not good.
别担心
Don't worry.
你来这是作为观察员，还让我找个后门
You're here as an observer and asking me for a back door.
还有别的不需我担心的事吗？
Is there anything else I shouldn't worry about?
有必要我会再联络的
I'll get in contact if necessary.
我要赶飞机
I have a plane to catch.
索马里
Somalia.
- 汉密尔顿？ - 罗伯・哈特？
- Hamilton? - Rob Hart?
好的，约法三章，第一：你要服从我指挥
Okay, three things. Firstly, you're under my command.
第二：你在这只是作为观察员
Secondly, you're here just as an observer.
第三，...嘿！
And thirdly ... hey!
第三：无论如何，我们会负责做事
Thirdly, we will do our job ... whatever happens.
- 做什么？ - 完成任务
And that is? - Complete the mission
- 你明白吗？ - 完全明白
- You understand? - Absolutely.
米勒，让他换件合适衣服
Miller, make sure he's dressed for the occasion.
跟我走
Follow me.
以防万一
In case things get serious.
让他呆在前面，老大
Make sure he stays up front boss.
- 你装的什么？ - 跟平常一样
- What do you have? - The usual.
- 没有异常吗？ - 没！
- Nothing unusual? No!
走吧
Go ahead.
- 走 - 关上门
- Go. - Close the door.
跟着我，钥匙，好的，集中注意力！
With me. Keys. Ok, keep focused!
我们走！
Let's go!
赶紧！
Hurry up!
快！
Come on!
快走！
Move!
把枪放下！
Put it down!
快，快！
Come on, come on!
走！
Go!
把枪放下！
Drop the gun!
他在哪儿？
Where is he?
是他
It's him.
你是谁？
Who are you?
美国人在哪儿？
Where's the American?
嘿
Hey.
嘿，我们完事了！
Hey, we're done here!
你别说话！懂吗？
You say nothing! You understand?
好的
Ok.
- 放下枪 - 放下枪！
- Drop the gun. - Gun Down!
放下武器
Put down your weapon.
什么？你以为我们找不到你？
What? You thought we wouldn't find you?
我告诉你吧
Let me make something perfectly clear.
你他妈就是个叛徒！
You're a fucking traitor!
你现在要把我怎样？
What are you going to do to me now?
你是谁？
Who are you?
- 喝吧！ - 你是瑞典人
- Drink! - You're Swedish ...
喝吧！你脱水了
Drink! You're dehydrated.
等你回到瑞典会有许多问题等着你
There's going to be many questions asked when you return to Sweden.
你没到埃塞俄比亚工作，你懂我在说什么吗？
You have not been in Ethiopia to work, do you understand what I'm saying?
-  我知道，我知道 - 听着！
- I know, I know ... - Listen!
否则就成了你是因北佛斯才跟被偷的武器有关的
It looks like you're involved with stolen weapons for North Fors.
- 我不知道，我只是负责训练他们 - 他们是谁？
- I didn't know. I just trained them. - Who's "them?"
塞彻贡
Sectragon.
两天前天幕炮弹袭击了埃塞俄比亚的一个目标
Two days ago Sky Shadow shell struck a target in Ethiopia,
从索马里发射的
it was fired from Somalia.
该死
Oh fuck ...
那他说的是真的
Then it's true, what he said.
谁？
Who?
本杰明・里
Benjamin Lee.
你隔壁牢房的那个人？
- The man who sat in the cell next to you?
是的
- Yes.
他为塞彻贡做事
He worked for Sectragon,
他逃跑是想告诉当局
He ran off to tell the authorities that
他们在索马里训练恐怖分子
they have trained terrorists in Somalia.
好的
Ok.
现在怎么办？
What's going to happen now?
我们回家去
We're going home.
我们要带他们去哪儿？
Where are we taking them?
你跟米勒走，米勒，带他去旅馆
You go with Miller, Miller take him to the hotel.
快，我们要出发了！
Come on we're moving out!
拉格贝克怎么办？
What about Lagerback?
你已经尽职了，拉格贝克会在几天内回家
You've done your bit. Lagerback will be home in a few days.
- 好的 - 嘿！
- Ok. - Hey!
你忘东西了吧？
You forgetting something?
塞彻贡总部，达拉斯
Sectragon Headquarters. Dallas.
你好
Yes.
喂？
Hello?
史密斯？我是哈特，长官...
Smith? It's Hart here sir ...
等一下，长官...
Hold on sir ...
长官！
Sir!
监狱救援任务完成了
The prison extraction is complete.
瑞典人和里救出来了
The Swede and Lee are out.
- 有别人跟他谈过吗？ - 没有，长官！
- Has anyone else talked to him? - No sir!
直升机现在来了
The helo's coming in now.
是，长官！
Yes sir!
- 好的，你知道怎么做吗？ - 是的，长官！
- Well, do you know what to do? - Yes sir!
处理好这事
Take care of it.
- 做掉他 - 好的
- Take care of him. Ok.
塞彻贡总部，达拉斯
Sectragon Headquarters, Dallas.
我们需要“自由行事”权
We require freedom of movement.
有个人我们要找回来
There is an individual we need to retrieve.
以防引起麻烦
Without creating any problems.
可以安排下吗？
Can that be arranged?
你想怎样？
What did you have in mind?
我想让他上黑名单
I would like to see his name on the list.
你帮塞彻贡做什么的？
What did you do for Sectragon?
相信我
Trust me.
要么我就把你丢这，你选吧
Or I leave you out here, your choice.
我负责情报工作
My field was information.
在情报部
Intelligence service.
黑色行动，你到底是谁？ （指机密任务，参考《使命召唤》）
Black operations. Who the hell are you?
我是瑞典情报部门的指挥官
I'm a Commander in the Swedish Intelligence Service.
关于阿富汗失踪炮弹你知道些什么？
What do you know about the missing shells in Afghanistan?
带我跟你去瑞典
Take me to Sweden with you,
我就告诉你所有我知道的
and I'll tell you all I know.
其中一枚干掉了在埃塞俄比亚的
One was used to take out an exiled
索马里流亡政治家
Somalian politician in Ethiopia.
萨马塔・拉希姆
Samata Rahim.
我曾试图阻止
I tried to stop that.
所以我弄成这样
That's why I'm here.
为什么塞彻贡要在索马里培养恐怖分子？
Why is Sectragon supplying terrorists in Somalia?
他们已准备好去世界各地了
They are prepared to go all the way.
需要的话他们会使用任何必要手段
By any means necessary if they have to.
我不会再说一个字了
I'm not saying another word.
要么你带我去瑞典
Either you take me to Sweden with you ...
要么你把我留在这，你选吧
Or you leave me here. Your choice.
我们会保护你的
We'll protect you.
你别动
You stay put.
汉密尔顿先生？我是查德
Mr. Hamilton? I'm Chad.
莫娜让我代她问好
Mona sends her regards.
跟我走吧
So walk with me.
里，这是查德
Lee, this is Chad.
你跟他走
You go with him.
我们待会在阿曼碰面
We'll meet later in Amman.
斯德哥尔摩
Stockholm.
瑞典政府已安排遭绑架的马丁・拉格贝克回国
The Government has been able to get kidnapped Martin Lagerback home.
他曾在索马里遭囚禁
He was been imprisoned in Somalia.
伊斯兰激进组织青年党
And the militant
Islamist group Al-Shabab
今天声称对索马里流亡政治家
took credit today for the murder of the exiled Somali
萨马塔・拉希姆和他家人遭袭事件负责
politician Samata Rahim and his family.
埃塞俄比亚情报部门认为此次袭击
The Ethiopian intelligence service thinks the strike took place
使用了称作天幕的瑞典制GPS制导炮弹
with a Swedish GPS guided shell known as a Sky Shadow.
美国军方领导表示该地区情势令人担忧
U.S. military leaders think the development in the area is disturbing.
基地组织和青年党都在索马里根基稳固
Both Al Qaeda and Al-Shabab have strong roots in Somalia.
而现在他们手握高科技武器
And they now have high-tech weapons
及其使用方法
and knowledge of how to use them.
非洲问题专家简・埃里克・兰姆佛斯表示
This implies a changing power shift, according to the
这意味着该地势力格局正发生改变
African Foreign Ministry expert, Jan Erik Ramfors.
我要你彻查到底
I want you to get to the bottom of this.
我要你去调查
I want you to investigate
北佛斯工业近年来涉及到的所有生意
all business that North Fors Industries has been involved in in recent years.
我想知道这到底是怎么发生的
I want to know exactly how this happened.
你认为克拉斯・奥洛夫松掌握着我们不知道的事情？
Do you think Clas Olofsson knows something we don't?
他觉得救回拉格贝克非常轻松
He was very relaxed about getting home Lagerback.
若结果证明其中有任何违法行为
If it turns out that there have been any illegalities
我可不想从电视里听到
I don't want to find out about it on TV.
是
Yes.
哈喽？
Hello?
嗨
Hi
嘿，我是警局的安娜・如纳
Hey, I'm Anna Rune from the police.
我想知道你是否...
I wonder if you ...
认识这个女人？
recognize this woman?
认识，她来过这儿，跟一个男的，他们就坐在那儿
Yes, she was here, with some man... They sat there.
好的，这个男的...
Okay, this man had ...
阿曼，约旦
Amman, Jordan.
- 我们不是该明天见面吗？ - 是的
- Aren't we supposed to meet tomorrow? - Yes.
但是塔里克有些疑问
But Tareq has some questions.
- 塔里克？ - 谁是本杰明・里？
- Tareq? - Who is Benjamin Lee?
他为塞彻贡工作
He worked for Sectragon.
他有关乎瑞典国家安全的情报
He has information regarding Swedish security.
他替他们卖命？
He works for them?
那他怎么上了美国的恐怖分子名单？
So how come he's listed as a terrorist in the U.S.?
任何帮助本杰明・里的人都会被视为恐怖分子
Anyone that helps Benjamin Lee will be tagged as a terrorist.
塞彻贡关系深厚，所以他才上了名单
Sectragon has contacts, that's why he's on that list.
名单的目的在于吓唬你这种人
The purpose of that list is to scare people like you.
你记得查德吗？
Do you remember Chad?
是啊
Yea.
那个在索马里帮你的人
The guy who helped you in Somalia.
他失踪了
He's missing.
如果查德开口，汉密尔顿先生
If Chad talks, Mr. Hamilton,
这就不止关系到你了
it's not going to be about you.
巴解组织必须置身事外 （巴勒斯坦解放组织）
The PLO must be out of this.
我们要用里来换查德
We will trade Lee for Chad.
塔里克，拜托
Tareq, please.
我能和莫娜单独呆会吗？
Can I have a moment alone with Mona?
别再讨论这事了
Don't discuss it any further.
这跟我们无关
This is none of our business.
好的，塔里克，我会处理的
Ok, Tareq. I will handle this.
我希望我们尽快结束这事，汉密尔顿先生
I hope we finish this soon, Mr. Hamilton.
- 拜 - 拜
- Bye. - Bye.
你知道自己惹了世上最大的佣兵部队吗？
Are you aware that you have provoked the largest private army in the world?
嗯，我知道
Well, it crossed my mind.
我找不到任何他跟塞彻贡有关的信息，所以
I could not find any information to link him to Sectragon, so
塔里克说得对
Tareq is right.
这不关我们的事，巴解组织
This is none of our business and the PLO
绝不可以跟恐怖分子有瓜葛
must not be associated with terrorists.
他不是恐怖分子
He is not a terrorist.
你觉得我不相信他的话我还会来吗？
Do you think I'd be here if I didn't believe in him?
他们不会放过你的，知道吗？
They're not going to leave you, you know?
等这事完了他们就会来追杀你
They're going to come after you when this is over.
你知道我干这行已经20多年了
You know I've been in this business for over 20 years now,
一般来说，我都该退休了
Statistically, my time is up.
我需要用你的关系把里弄出约旦
I need your contacts to get Lee out of the country.
我需要你相信我
I need you to trust me.
我相信
I do.
索马里
Somalia.
冈萨尔斯，起来！
Gonzalez ... Up!
你有个妹妹
You've got a sister,
快招，否则下一个就是她了
talk or she'll be here next.
在阿曼...
In Amman ...
跟谁一起？
With who?
想象下你的妹妹在这跟我一起吧...
Think about your sister ... Here with me.
你在阿曼的联络人是谁？
Who's your contact in Amman?
莫娜...
Mona ...
莫娜・阿尔法沙和一个男的
Mona Al-Fatha. And a man.
阿曼，约旦
Amman, Jordan.
萨拉姆・阿雷库目
Salam Aleikum.
里在哪？你带我去找他
Where is Lee. You take me to him.
- 看来要下次了 - 你失败过一次了
- Another time. - You failed before.
乌兹别克斯坦和阿富汗的边境
The border between Uzbekistan and Afghanistan.
原来是你
It was you.
等我干掉里
When I'm finished with Lee,
我就去找你
I'm coming for you.
这是上帝的旨意
As God wants.
喂
Hello.
你看到他了？
You got him?
我可以干掉汉密尔顿，重复，我可以干掉汉密尔顿
I can take out Hamilton, repeat, I can take out Hamilton.
不，他能带我们找到里，我们待会再干掉他
No, he'll lead us to Lee. We'll take him out later.
喂
Hello.
帮我叫塔里克
Call me Tareq.
狙击手去右边楼顶了，快走！
Sniper to the right on the roof. Go!
塔里克快上车！快！
Tareq hurry to the car! Quick!
上车，塔里克！
The car Tareq!
塔里克！
Tareq!
里怎么样了？
What about Lee?
你干掉他了？
Did you get him?
塔里克
Tareq.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
如果要人们为你牺牲性命
If people are going to sacrifice their lives for you...
我想知道为什么
I want to know why.
为什么我朋友会死？
Why is my friend dead?
我说，回答我！你知道什么？
I said, answer me! What do you know?
别这样
Don't do it.
我希望值得救他
I hope he's worth it.
等在这
Wait here.
坐吧
Sit.
愿主令他安息
May God have mercy on his soul.
看着他们，我马上回来
Keep an eye on them. I'll be right back.
我真的很感谢你给我的帮助
I really appreciate all the help you've given me.
我利用跟莫娜的友情来救你
I used my friendship with Mona to save your life.
那么现在，我要你
So now, I want you
告诉我所有你知道的
tell me everything you know.
战争对于塞彻贡这样的组织来说利润丰厚
War is extremely profitable for an organization like Sectragon.
五角大楼在伊拉克已经支付了超过100亿美元给私人军事承包商
Pentagon has fed over $10 billion to private contractors in Iraq.
青年党将再次发动袭击
The world is waiting for Al-Shabab to strike again.
而我知道时间和地点
And I know when and where that'll happen.
哈特的队伍会执行这次行动
Hart's team will carry out the operation.
不过青年党会为此负责
But Al-Shabab will get the blame.
他们要做什么？
What will they do?
等我安全了我就给你更多情报
I'll give you more information when I'm in safety.
你在中情局的恐怖分子名单上
You are on the CIA's terrorist list.
塞彻贡跟中情局有关系
Sectragon has contacts in the CIA.
我能做什么？
- What can I do?
要求跟我们的首相谈话吧
- Demand to speak to our extra trial Prime Minister.
这是你唯一脱身的机会
That's your only chance to get through to the right people.
好的
Ok.
机场受到监视了
The airport is under surveillance.
所以我们要带你去大马士革，你从那起飞
So we take you to Damascus. You fly from there.
阿布・奥马，给我点东西盖上他
Abu Omar, give me something to cover him.
斯德哥尔摩群岛
Stockholm's archipelago.
里先生，欢迎
Mr. Lee ... Welcome.
现在没你的事了，汉密尔顿
Your business is finished now, Hamilton.
这边请
This way please.
我已经跟你说了，长官
I've already told you sir,
除非我能直接跟首相对话
Only if I can speak directly with the prime minister
我才会说出任何关于塞彻贡的情报
will I speak about any information concerning Sectragon.
我认为你的谈判手段并不高明
I don't think your negotiation tactics serves you well,
因为中情局发现你处于瑞典保护
beacause it's only a matter of time before the
之前只是时间问题
CIA finds out that you in Swedish custody.
你得牢记这点！
You remember that!
是有件事，她后来晚上给我打了电话
There was one thing, she called me later in the night.
她忘带她的电脑了，想让我保管好
She had forgotten her computer and wanted me to look after it.
- 你现在有吗？ - 是的，这边
- Do you have it here? - Yes, come here.
额，这是那个跟玛丽一起的男人
Ehm, this is the man who was there with Mary.
我们有两个目击者能证实
We have two witnesses who can verify it.
我想知道我是否能在媒体上公布这个照片？
I want to know if I can publish this picture in the press?
- 等一会 - 为什么？
- Wait for a bit. - Why?
额，我得核实些事情
Ehh ... There's something I have to check.
核实什么？
Check what?
我说的不够清楚吗？我说的你还有不明白的吗？
Was I unclear? Was there anything I said you don't understand?
- 你知道凶手是谁，是吗？ - 先别管了，别管了
- You know who it is don't you? - Back off for now, back off.
北佛斯工业，斯德哥尔摩
North Fors Industries, Stockholm.
外交部没批准过任何
The Foreign Ministry has not approved any
非法终端用户证书
end-user certificates that have not been correct.
没有任何“私下交易”
There are no "hidden appointments"
没有贿赂，没有跟北佛斯有关的走私案
no bribes ... No smuggling that can be connected to North Fors.
调查期间只会发现一个小细节
There's just one small detail that will show up during an investigation.
什么？
What?
是你一年前促成了
That it was you who pushed through the Sky
与匈牙利的天幕出售合约
Shadow agreement with Hungary a year ago.
是的，不过那完全是照章办事
Yes, but it was completely by the book.
- 是的 - 是的
- Yes. - Yes.
而现在它们失踪了
And now they are gone.
你却还没收到钱
And you have not been paid.
现在青年党正在索马里使用它们
And now they are being used by Al-Shabab in Somalia.
但是，但是等一下，你到底在说什么啊？
But, but wait a minute, what the hell are you saying now?
什么？克拉斯，什么意思？
What? Clas, what the hell?
瑞典情报部正保护一个男人
Swedish intelligence has a man in their custody.
他知道这一切
He knows all about this.
- 好的，那，那他是谁？ - 他叫本杰明・里
- Yes, and, and who is it? - His name is Benjamin Lee.
他要说出他所知的一切
And he's going to tell everything he knows.
本杰明・里需要瑞典政府的保证
So Benjamin Lee will need guarantees from the Swedish government.
- 他想要一个新身份和保护 - 嗯
- He wants a new identity and protection. - Mmmm.
他只会跟你私下直接对话
And he will only talk directly with you, personally.
好的，这没问题
Well that's not a problem.
不幸的是
Well unfortunately,
美国已经把他列为恐怖分子
the U.S. has listed him as a terrorist.
本杰明・里知道
Benjamin Lee knows,
他们是如何一步步将非洲之角引入战争边缘
how step by step they are setting the stage for a war in Horn of Africa.
但是这些都是恐怖分子说的
But these claims come from a terrorist.
有什么证据吗？
Is there any evidence?
没！
No!
- 本杰明・里是可信的 - 他可信？
- Benjamin Lee is credible. - So, he's credible?
我们要忽视中情局的信息吗？
Are we suppossed to ignore information that comes from the CIA?
塞彻贡在策划一次暗杀
Sectragon is planning an assassination
要让恐怖分子背这黑锅
where the blame is placed on terrorists.
到时候，这地区的战争就不可避免了
When it happens, a war in the region is inevitable.
找他来谈吧
Get him to talk.
周二，约瑟夫・贝克勒会出席和平会议
On Tuesday, Joseph Bekele will be at the peace conference.
我要知道本杰明・里了解的所有情况
I want to know everything that Benjamin Lee knows.
据美国军方高层称
According to sources in American military leadership
索马里正举行一系列有计划的军事演习
there is a planned a series of military exercises in Somalia.
一直致力于推动非洲之角
Ethiopia's prime minister, Josef Bekele
国家间和平发展的
who has worked for a peaceful development
埃塞俄比亚总理约瑟夫・贝克勒
between countries in the Horn of Africa,
对该地区未来表示了担忧
is worried about the future of the region,
他担心国家间将出现新的暴力冲突
and fears new violence between countries.
现在再把目光转向玛利亚・索斯卡医生
And we continue now with new information
谋杀案的最新消息
about the murder of Dr. Maria Solska.
据警方发言人称，已有确切证据
According to a police spokesman, certain evidence has been found
证明此案与波兰有关
that shows there's a link to Poland
玛利亚・索斯卡近年来曾11次前往该国
where Maria Solska had visited 11 times in recent years.
卡尔！
Carl!
我要你跟里谈谈
I want you to talk to Lee.
我的新上司说没我的事了
My new boss says I'm finished with it.
你是唯一能让他开口的人
You're the only one who can get him to talk.
你是唯一本杰明信任的人
You are the only one Benjamin trusts.
曾有个人也信任我，但她现在死了
There was another person who trusted me, but she's dead now.
忘了玛利亚・索斯卡吧
Let Maria Solska go.
这是个意外
It was an accident.
这他妈不是意外，是条件反射
That was no fucking accident, it was a reflex.
你也很清楚这点
You know that as well.
20年来我一直在训练掌握它
I've been training to master it for 20 years.
它救了我很多次
It has saved my life many times.
一瞬间，我就杀了玛丽
It only took a split second ... I killed Mary.
你错了
You're wrong.
明天
Tomorrow ...
我要去自首
I'm turning myself in.
你确实有理由置身事外
You stand outside the system, and there's a good reason for it.
但在必要时你得保护国家利益
You should protect the nation's interests, when necessary.
我为了国家利益受训杀人
I am trained to kill in the nation's interest.
但是我做不到
But I can't.
我再也做不到了
I can't anymore.
我爱她
I loved her.
你明白吗？
Do you understand?
也许正如你所说玛丽死于条件反射
Mary's death was perhaps ... a reflex as you say.
但是正是条件反射救了本杰明・里的命
But the same reflex saved
Benjamin Lee's life.
所以我让你跟里谈谈
So I ask you talk to Lee.
去警察局前先把这事办了
Do it before going to the police.
你太迟了
You're too late.
我已经告诉他们所有有关袭击的事了
I already told them everything about the attack.
你跟谁说了？
Who have you told?
谁？
Who?
本杰明・里不见了
Benjamin Lee is gone.
下一步这样，我跟你和法曼碰面
Here's what we'll do, I will meet you and Vernman
我们有内奸，否则塞彻贡永远也找不到他
We have a leak ... Otherwise Sectragon would never have found him.
我们必须把他抢回来
We must get him back.
不，我来处理
No. I'll handle this.
现在我要照自己的方式来干
I do this my way now.
卡尔，你是为我做事的
Carl, you work for me.
你等我消息
You'll hear from me.
你不能单干
You can't do this alone.
我不是一个人
I'm not alone.
你能给我解释下到底
Can you explain to me how the hell
塞彻贡怎么发现他在这的？
Sectragon could find him here?
你怎么知道是他们？
How do you know it was them?
还能是谁？
Who else could it be?
监控文件丢了
The monitoring files are gone.
该死
Damn.
谢谢
Thanks.
托马斯，我能跟你谈谈吗？
Thomas, can I have a word with you?
本杰明・里不见了，他可能死了
Benjamin Lee is gone. He may be dead.
三个负责他安全的瑞典士兵被杀
Three Swedish soldiers responsible for his safety were killed.
有人泄露了他的位置
Someone leaked where he was.
好吧
Well.
不，但是怎么...
No, but what ...
只有我和你知道他在哪里
It was only you and I who knew where he was.
天啊，萨拉，你在怀疑我吗？
But my god Sara, are you accusing me?
本杰明・里是个遭通缉的恐怖分子，我们都知道的
Benjamin Lee is a wanted terrorist, that's all we know.
我们怎么能肯定不是情报部门某个人泄露了消息？
How do we know for sure that someone from our own Intelligence Service didn't do it?
或者，或者是本杰明・里杀了士兵之后跑了
Or, or if it was Benjamin Lee who killed our men and then ran ...
我们不能肯定
We don't know this.
是不能
No.
但是我会查清楚的
But I'll figure it out now.
谢谢你帮我
Thank you for helping me.
我是为了塔里克才干的
I'm doing this for Tareq.
- 那，你就躲在这？ - 是
- So, this is where you hide out? - Yea.
看见没？
See that?
那里
There.
那是哈特
That's Hart.
是的，但是他怎么找到里的？
Yea, but how did he find Lee?
有内奸吗？
Is there a leak?
是的，很明显
Yea, apparently.
但是我从没听说什么袭击
But I never heard a word about an attack.
- 是啊，那他在撒谎了 - 他是为了求生
- Yea, but he's lying. - He had to survive.
只要哈特知道这点就会杀了他
And as soon as Hart realizes this, he will kill him.
所以我们去找哈特
So we go for Hart.
他会指引我们找到里
He will lead the way to Lee.
你认识她？
Did you know her?
是，她被杀了
Yea ... she was murdered.
谁干的？
Who did it?
发生了什么？
So what happened?
玛利亚・索斯卡？
Maria Solska?
她跟这事有关吗？
Is she involved with this?
她给塞彻贡做事吗？
Did she work for Sectragon?
不
No.
是你的错吗？
Was it your fault?
我割了她的喉咙
I slit her throat.
我能相信你吗？
Can I trust you?
什么？
What?
如果我们碰见哈特，打了起来
If we meet Hart and it comes to combat ...
我能相信你吗？
Can I trust you?
“我干这行已经快20年了”
"I've been doing this for almost 20 years now."
“一般来说，我都该退休了”
"Statistically, my time is up,"
这是你在阿曼对我说的，对吧？
- You said that to me back in Amman, didn't you?
是我说的
- Yes, I did.
那么，这就是你的愿望？
So, is that what you prefer?
死在哈特手下？
A bullet from Hart?
但是我可不想这样，卡尔
But this doesn't work for me, Carl.
你知道吗
You know ...
我开始想象跟她一起的生活
I started to imagine a life with her ...
生活？
A life?
你是说就像普通生活那样？
You mean like just an ordinary life?
- 就像那样 - 卡尔！
- Like, a life. - Carl!
你就是你，为什么你不接受这些呢？
You are who you are, why can't you just accept it?
她是无辜的
She was innocent.
好吧，她不是唯一无辜的
Well she was not the only one.
目前，卡尔，我只想知道
And right now Carl, the only thing I want to know is
我是否能相信你
I can trust you or not.
- 你明白吗？ - 是的
- Do you understand ? Yes
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
我在家，我们需要了解你知道什么
I'm at home, we need to know what you know.
给我回电
So call me.
你好！我找卡尔・汉密尔顿
Hello! I am looking for Carl Hamilton.
干嘛？
What is it?
你没正面回答我的问题
That's a very vague answer to my question
约翰娜，好的，请进
Johanna ... Yes, come in..
- 卡尔在家吗？ - 不
- Is Carl at home? - No.
你可以跟我说，我是他父亲
You can speak with me, I'm his father.
这孩子做什么了？
What has the boy done now?
你不是他父亲
You are not his dad.
你怎么查到他的？
How did you track him?
通过你
Through you.
我跟你上司谈过了
I talked with your boss,
我们昨天碰面后去看望了他
and then came to visit him when we met yesterday.
会面的起因就在于你
The reason for the meeting was initiated by you.
我看到你了
I saw you.
我在等你现身
I was just waiting for you to show up.
卡尔杀了一个女人，你认为保护他对吗？
Carl has killed a woman, do you think it's right to protect him?
如果真是这样的话
If this did happen,
汉密尔顿是我们最有价值的人才
Hamilton is one of our most valuable assets.
所以现在我跟你说，我只说一次
So now I ask you, and I ask only once
忘掉这个小过错吧
forget about this little crusade ...
那么你认为我该不管这事？
So you think I should just drop it?
我说过一次了，不重复第二次！
One time I said, not two!
可以走了吗？
Shall we go?
塞彻贡总部，达拉斯
Sectragon Headquarters, Dallas.
里已经开口了
Lee has been talking.
影响如何？
And the damage?
- 相对较小 - 尽力弥补吧
- Relatively small. - Do what you have to.
如果这牵涉到瑞典首相呢？
And if it involves the Swedish Prime Minister?
约瑟夫・贝克勒会死的...只是不照原计划而已
Josef Bekele will die ... Just not how we planned it.
不过他的死仍会造成同样的影响
But his death will have exactly the same impact.
你看，灵活多变就是我们这行基础
You see, flexibility is the cornerstone of our profession.
只要我们保持灵活性，就掌握控制权
If we remain flexible, we maintain control.
- 控制权？ - 青年党会对此负责
- Control? - Al-Shabab will take the blame.
而新的埃塞俄比亚政府会加入我们
And the new Ethiopian government will join us
参与反恐战争
in the war against terror.
斯德哥尔摩
Stockholm.
- 嗨！
- 上午好
Hi!
- Good morning.
- 我早前打过电话订了房间 - 是的
- I called earlier and made a reservation. - Yes.
房间能看到大桥吗？
Is this a room with a view of the bridge?
当然，先生，我们帮你安排好了
Absolutely sir, we arranged that for you.
在5083房间
It's room 5083.
欢迎里先生
Welcome Mr. Lee.
我们检查下计时器
Let's check the timings.
全部设置好了
All set and clear.
蓝色雷克萨斯车
Blue Lexus.
嘭
Boom.
一切正常，进入下一步
We're good to go.
- 唾液和口水在上面了？ - 是的
- Saliva and DNA on this? - Yea.
好的
Good.
嘿！
Hey!
这威力太大了，会炸掉半个酒店的
It's too big, it'll take out half the hotel.
不会，这腰带有结构缺陷
No, there's a construction flaw in the belt.
他的部分头部和躯干会保持完整
Parts of his head and torso will remain intact.
给你腰带，长官
The belt sir.
哈特，哈特，你在干嘛？
Hart. Hart, wuts you doing?
- 哈特，拜托，听我说 - 我们开战了
- Hart, please, listen to me. - We are at war.
你记得吗？
You remember that?
拜托
- Please ...
约瑟夫・贝克勒将为伟大事业而死
- Josef Bekele will die, for the greater good.
为了让世界看清恐怖分子势力稳固会有什么后果
For the world to see what happens when terrorism takes a foothold.
是你自作自受
You brought this on yourself.
在你炸死自己前，你会干掉两个国家首脑
You'll take out two heads of state, before you blow up yourself up.
在你转头反抗我们时
You didn't see that coming, did you?
你没预见到这点吧，对吗？
When you turned yourself against us.
你是谁？
Who the hell are you?
等等
Wait ...
你有用过武器吗？
Have you ever used weapons?
你有杀过人吗？
Have you killed anyone?
16个人死在了乌兹别克斯坦和阿富汗边境
Sixteen people died on the border between Uzbekistan and Afghanistan.
一个家庭被天幕迫击炮炸死了
A family was wiped out by a Sky Shadow mortar
就在索马里
in Somalia.
是你杀了他们
You murdered them.
你没按下按钮
You didn't press the button
但你杀了他们
but you murdered them.
本杰明・里在哈特劫走他之前告诉了我一切
Benjamin Lee explained everything to me before Hart kidnapped him.
如果你不自首，说出一切
If you do not turn yourself in... And tell everything
我会回来找你的，我发誓！
I'll come back. I promise!
你明白我说什么吗？
Do you understand what I'm saying?
- 哈特！我们得见个面 - 发生什么了？
- Hart! We have to meet. - What happened?
有个男的闯进我办公室威胁要杀了我
A man came into my office and threatened to kill me.
他知道一切
- He knew everything.
听着，你要镇静，听见没？
- Listen, you keep your shit together, you hear me?
- 跟我在树林路旁停车处碰面 - 好的
- Meet me at the lay by in the woods. - Ok.
他们上钩了
They took the bait.
谢谢贝克勒先生光临瑞典
Thank you Mr. Bekele for coming to Sweden.
是我的荣幸
It is my pleasure.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
- 他知道些什么？ - 他知道你劫走了里
- What did he know? - He knew about you kidnapping Lee.
- 什么时候的事？ - 大约30分钟前
- When did it happen? - About 30 minutes ago ...
- 米勒 - 是，长官
- Miller. - Yes sir.
- 我们旁边没人吗？ - 不，汉密尔顿在跟踪
- Are we alone? - No, Hamilton is following.
“包裹”已准时出发
The package is on time for delivery.
现在回歌乐酒店去！
Get back to the hotel Clarion now!
好的，他死定了
Sure. He's a dead man.
快出去！
Out!
问题解决了，我们走！
Problem solved ... Let's go!
开车！
Go!
我去找狙击手
I go for sniper
你干掉另一个
you take the other one.
狗日的！
Son of a bitch!
还有10分钟
Ten minutes.
起来！起来！
Get up! Get up!
枪扔了，否则我就割开她的喉咙
Drop it, or I'll cut her throat.
- 打他 - 闭上臭嘴！
- Shoot him ... - Shut the fuck up!
- 打他！ - 扔了枪，否则她死定了
- Shoot him! - Drop it, or she's dead.
没事了
It's good,
我很好
I'm ok.
子弹穿过去了，穿过去了
It went right through, right through.
你会没事的
You will be fine.
我们得走了！得走了！
We gotta go! Gotta go!
我们知道使用了瑞典武器
We know that Swedish weapons were used.
北佛斯工业牵扯其中...
North Fors Industries are involved ...
塞彻贡负责开展行动
and Sectragon carried the operation out.
塞彻贡？
Sectragon?
卡尔
Carl,
你知道他在哪，而且他以为你死了
you know where he is and he thinks you're dead.
你必须去看医生
You must see a doctor.
你知道怎么做
You know what to do.
米勒，回话
Miller, come in.
米勒！
Miller!
米勒，回话
Miller, come in.
等等
Wait ...
卡尔，要活着回来
Carl, please come back.
- 有消息吗？ - 没
- Heard anything? - No
该死
Shit.
多久了？
How long?
4分钟
Four minutes.
打这个号码就能炸掉大桥
This number will blow the bridge
然后你得在一小时内赶到集合点
then you've got one hour to get to the assembly point.
- 我们动手吧！是，长官 - 祝你好运！
- Let's do this!Yes sir. - Good luck!
来啊！
Let's Rock!
我炸死里
I blow up Lee ...
我们会同归于尽
we both die.
这就是你要的？
Is that what you want?
莫娜・阿尔法沙
Mona Al-Fatha,
她在外面车里
she was in a car outside.
我们抓到她了
We have her.
我打个电话
I make a call ...
你救到她，我自己离开，问题就解决了
you have her, I walk ... Problem solved.
我是说真的
I mean what I say.
现在我要拿我的手机
Now I need my telephone ...
拿吧
Do it.
打电话
Make the call.
小心点
Careful ...
5083房间
Room 5083.
证据都在那儿
Everything is there.
- 你在这干嘛？ - 我想跟你谈谈
- What are you doing here? - I wanted to talk to you.
不会有什么判决的
It's not going to happen.
玛利亚死了，因为我是特工
Maria died ... because I am who I am.
我不会接受审判的
I'm not going to be judged.
但是我余生都得活在这阴影里
But I will live with this ... the rest of my life.
因为涉及国家利益
It is in the national interest
所以这是个高度机密
that it is a well-kept secret.
是的
Yes.
确实涉及国家利益
It is fact in the nation's interest.
我来这是请你忘了此事
I'm here to ask you to let it go.
等等
Wait ...
这个
here.
是你的
It's yours.